[Music]
smile and learn
hello friends do you like animals
i love them today we're going to learn
about
wild animals
i came by searching for them but it's
already nighttime i'll use my torch to
find them
there's a silhouette over there which
animal would that be
[Music]
it's a lion
lion
the lion is the king of the jungle
[Music]
i see another silhouette over there
let's find out what animal that is
it's an
elephant elephant
the elephant is huge
elephant
let's see what other animals we can spot
it's a giraffe giraffe
that's quite a neck isn't it
giraffe
let's see what we'll find in this tree
[Music]
it's a
monkey monkey
monkeys are so funny
monkey
[Music]
let's see what's down there
it's a crocodile
crocodile
look at those teeth
there's another silhouette what would
that be
a gorilla
gorilla
gorillas are very strong
[Music]
let's keep searching for animals over
here
[Music]
a zebra
zebra
zebra stripes are so cool
[Music]
let's see if we can spot more wild
animals
a tiger
tiger
tigers are fierce
what else have we got here
a rhinoceros
rhinoceros
my my look at that horn
[Music]
let's see if there's another animal
around
sure there is
[Applause]
a bear
bear
how big is that bear
i think there's one more animal around
here
a wolf
wolf
i love wolves
have you seen how many animals are there
let's recap so you won't forget them
lion
elephant
giraffe
monkey
[Music]
crocodile
gorilla
[Music]
zebra
tiger
rhinoceros
bear
wolf
that's all friends
i think it's time to go back home
do you want to keep on learning try for
free our smile and learn platform for a
month and enjoy all of our games videos
and interactive stories
go for it download smile and learn on
your mobile tablet or pc