Color
red
The color is red.
blue
The color is blue.
red and blue
purple
Red and blue make purple.
yellow
The color is yellow.
blue and yellow
green
Blue and yellow make green.
yellow and red
orange
Yellow and red make orange.
red, blue, and yellow
black
Red, blue, and yellow make black.
red
purple
blue
green
yellow
orange
black
red
The color is red.
white
The color is white.
red and white
pink
Red and white make pink.
black
The color is black.
white and black
gray
White and black make gray.
orange
The color is orange.
black and orange
brown
Black and orange make brown.
red
pink
white
gray
black
brown
orange
We are living in a colorful world!
rainbow
red
orange
yellow
green
blue
indigo
violet
red
orange
yellow
green
blue
indigo
violet
These are rainbow colors!