Laaaaaaa!!!!!!!!!!!
Hi kids
Let's all count from one to twenty
We'll count from one to twenty three times
and each time we'll count faster
Count, count, count with me
Count with me from one to twenty
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Twenty
Great job kids!
Let's count again faster
Count, count, count with me
Count with me from one to twenty
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Twelve
Thirteen
Fourteen
Fifteen
Sixteen
Seventeen
Eighteen
Nineteen
Twenty
Outstanding!
Let's count again even faster
Count, count, count with me
Count with me from one to twenty
One, two, three, four, five
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen
Sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty